Personal Information:

Name: Lukas Bunat

Address: **Prague, Czech Republic**

E-mail: lukas.bunat@gmail.com

Phone number: [CZE] +420 731 277 533

Website: www.lukasbunat.net

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/lukasbunat/



Personal Statement:

I have had gradually studied at four different universities in Europe and Asia. In recent years have shaped my opinions, and developed my passions. I have gained many skills and abilities during this period too. I love traveling, especially having cross-culture experiences and listening to/learning about new and an unknown. Apart of that, I regularly play sports such as volleyball or floorball.

I have been told, I am good at finding clever solutions even if they are not obvious, yet still reflecting and implementing suggestions from others. I believe, my technically analytical thinking helps me in these cases. On top of that, I steadfastly hard-working towards my dreams and goals. But I have learnt, if you can't learn new things, cooperate in a team or communicate with others, no matter which country they are from, you will hardly achieve big things. I am the one, who always wants to lead others by using my own creativity. I want affect others in a positive way by relating to them.

Education:

2014 D		1 1 T	T . • • 4	D	C 1 D 11'
2014 - Present	C Zech I e	rnnical i	Iniversity	Prague	Czech Republic
2017 11C3C11t		.cmmcar v		Tiuzuc.	CZCCII ICCDUDIIC

Faculty of Information Technology, Information Systems and Management

03/2017 – 06/2017 **Kyungpook National University**, Daegu, South Korea

Exchange studies

07/2016 – 12/2016 **Indian Institute of Technology Madras**, Chennai, India

Exchange studies

03/2016 **Delft University of Technology**, Delft, Netherlands,

The ATHENS Programme, Case study of Earthquakes in Netherlands

07/2012 – 08/2012 **Mayflower College of English**, Plymouth, United Kingdom

Summer language school

2010 - 2014 High school of Communication Technology Panska, Prague, Czech Republic

Technical Lyceum, graduated (maturity diploma)

Work Experience:

10/2017 – 12/2017 Big Data Architect Trainee

Comillas Pontifical University ICAI-ICADE, Madrid, Spain

Application of Clustering Methods for Discovering Patterns of Energy

03/2017 – 06/2017 Network Engineer Trainee

Network Lab at Kyungpook National University, Deagu, South Korea

Work on Cooja simulator, Network simulations

09/2014 – 03/2015 Paper-Form Blueprints Convert

Cooperation with Project International a.s.

Converting paper form of blueprints into digital form using AutoCAD

http://www.projectint.cz/index.php

11/2011 - 01/2013 Financial Advisor

OVB Holding, Prague, Czech Republic

Providing financial services and financial advice, Customer Service

http://www.ovb.eu/english/

Other Experience:

2014 - Present **Buddy for new incoming international students**

Volunteer in International Student Club at Czech Technical University Helping to new incoming foreign students at CTU during their exchnage

03/2017 - 06/2017 Culture teacher

Teaching at Korean high schools about Czech and European culture

Projects:

2013 – 2014 The influence of insulation on the energy performance of the house

http://goo.gl/aW6EQQ

Language Proficiency:

Czech, Slovak: Native Speaker

English: Full professional proficiency, Advanced level

TOEIC L&R: 845 points, Erasmus+ OLS: C1

German, Spanish,

Korean

Basic passive knowledge

Skills:

Programming Languages: C++, C, Java, SQL, Bash, Python, PySpark, HTML, CSS, PHP, JS

Programs: AutoCAD, Autodesk Inventor, Wolfram Mathematica, TeXStudio,

Microsoft Office - Word, Exel, PowerPoint, Access

Networking: Routing, Network structure, configuration and administration,

Protocols, ISO model, IP Address Leasing, Routing

Administration: Knowledgeable about PC architecture, able to assemble and servis

computers. I can administrate Windows and Unix systems.

Soft Skills: Innovative analytical problem solving, Leadership with good decision

making, Projects' cycle management skills, Cross-culture communication skills, Adaptability, Team player, Strong opinions, Hard-working towards my dreams and goals, Cooperation and

communication with others, no matter their background

Certificates:

CISCO Academy CCNA 1 - Network Fundamentals

AutoDesk AutoCAD 2014, 2D drawing

Inventor Professional 2014, 3D modeling

UNESCO Cross Cultural Awareness Programme

Teaching Culture Differences at Korean High Schools in Daegu

Fitness Fitness Instructor

Hobbies

New trending innovative technologies, Travelling, Cross-culture encounters, Reading, Self-development, Sports (volleyball, floorball, badminton, fitness)

Lukás Burialt